Ancestor, I have a massive
secret to expose.
Imperial Physician Xiao has defiled
the inner court.
His crimes are unforgivable.
He had an affair with the Empress Dowager
in the Palace of Earthly Tranquility
and tried to hide the secret
of the royal heir.
This silver needle has the little
Emperor's blood on it.
What a biting dog.
Since you are willing to risk your life,
you will work for me from now on.
At the ceremony tonight,
you will be the killing knife
and bite the Empress Dowager
and Xiao Han to death for me.
I will not fail my mission.
What exactly did that woman
say to you in there?
Nothing.
You two were alone for two hours,
and you came out smelling like perfume.
You're telling me it's nothing?
You're being too secretive.
That's not cool.
Warning: Midnight has arrived.
Mandatory task:
The Ancestral Sacrifice and
Public Trial Ceremony has begun.
What is this? A death notice?
The good show is about to begin.
Halt.
Isn't this our arrogant
Imperial Physician Xiao?
Why are you still putting on airs
when you're about to die?
You rootless castrated dog.
Get lost,
or I'll bleed you first.
What are you so arrogant about?
You're just a fifth-rank guard.
I'm now the Chief Eunuch's favorite.
Xiao Han, tonight's ceremony
will be your death.
I want to see you chopped into meat paste
by the Iron Guards with my own eyes.
Just kick the dog out of the way.
Don't dirty your knife.
Empress Dowager.
The midnight ancestral sacrifice
ceremony is imminent.
According to the ancestral rules,
the new Emperor must offer incense and
report to the late Emperor's tomb,
acknowledge his ancestors,
and officially enter
the royal genealogy.
The time is approaching.
Please move to prepare, Your Grace.
Chief,
I want to expose Imperial Physician Xiao's
affair with the Empress Dowager.
That little Emperor is simply the bastard
of this dog physician.
Eunuch Chen, falsely accusing a court
official without evidence
will result in your tongue
being pulled out.
Still stubborn?
Chief Eunuch,
I have solid proof.
This silver needle
has the blood he left behind when he
treated that little bastard tonight.
left behind
And I saw with my own eyes outside the
window of the Palace of Earthly Tranquility
that Imperial Physician Xiao and the
Empress Dowager were half-undressed
and hugging tightly.
This is defiling the inner court.
His crimes are unforgivable.
Insolent! How can you take
the Emperor's bloodline
so lightly?
Empress Dowager,
I am terrified.
But this concerns the royal bloodline,
and no confusion can be tolerated.
Since someone has reported it publicly,
to silence the crowd,
we can only ask the little Emperor to take
a blood test to verify his paternity.
You can test it,
but if it turns out that this dog slave
deliberately framed him,
can you and he bear the capital crime
of slandering the royal heir?
If there is any mistake,
I am willing to apologize with my death.
Men, keep an eye on
Imperial Physician Xiao
and bring some water.
I'd like to see who dares.
You don't need to make a move.
I'll play with them.
Alum was added
to forcibly dissolve red blood cells.
Anyone's blood will blend in it.
They came prepared,
but it's just a cheap trick.
Physician Xiao,
please.
Whether you are innocent
or have defiled the inner palace,
it all depends on this drop of blood.
Make sure your hand doesn't shake.
Physician Xiao,
don't you usually boast about
your unparalleled medical skills
and act so high and mighty
in the Imperial Hospital?
Not daring to use the needle
means you have a guilty conscience.
Empress Dowager,
the evidence is irrefutable.
What else do you have to say?
Guards,
arrest this venomous woman
who defiled the inner palace,
along with this fake prince
and her paramour,
and execute them on the spot!
They are going to kill
the Empress Dowager.
Doesn't that mean we've completed
the system mission?
That mute lunatic
actually used herself as bait.
Whatever. Since I'm handsome
and kind-hearted,
I'll reluctantly protect you.
Chief,
there's no need to dirty your hands
with such a venomous woman.
I am willing to carry out justice
and behead her myself.
As long as I kill
the Empress Dowager myself,
the dungeon points will be mine.
Eunuch Chen is right.
My blade is always accurate.